

CONTACT

Atyrau, Kazakhstan (Ready to relocate)

+7 (775) 976-41-65

serikuly.zhassulan@gmail.com

in Link to the linkedin Link to the github

Telegram - young_flovver

ABOUT ME

Disciplined in terms of strict adherence to the rules set by the entrepreneur. Stress resistant. Reliable and self-organized, I respect the opinions of people and do not conflict. I may not be that experienced, but I am someone you will want to meet and work with. I take my job very seriously and can work both individually and in the team. I know how to organize and plan work on time and use every minute to my advantage. Have analytical skills, so quick and independent decision- making is my thing. Desire for professional development, self-improvement, professional growth and development helps me find myself in any circle. The ability to communicate with people of all ages and backgrounds provides me with quality relationships with colleagues. I love learning new things and expanding my horizons.

TARGET

Getting a permanent job in your company. To work honestly and conscientiously in accordance with the objectives of the company to achieve the set goals.

LANGUAGES

- Kazakh Native (C2)
- Russian Fluent (C1)
- English <u>Upper Intermediate</u> (B2)
- Turkish Upper Intermediate (B2)
- Chinese Conversant (A2)

SKILLS

- Java, C++, Python;
- HTML5, CSS3 (Less, SASS), JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, React js; MySQL, Oracle PL/SQL, R;
- Pandas, Matplotlib, NumPy, Seaborn;
- Adobe Photoshop / After Effects / Premiere Pro, iMovie, VN;
- Git, VS Code, IntelliJ IDEA, Sublime text, Cisco Packet Tracer, Tinkercad, Anaconda, Jupyter, DOSBox, Little Man Computer, Asana;
- Figma, Canva, Corel Draw, Fusion 360°;
- Docker, Jira;
- Agile, Scrum, Kanban;

ACHIEVEMENTS

- 2nd place in the Olympiad in Math (2013)
- 1st place in the Regional Olympiad in Informatics (2017)
- 2nd place in International Competition <u>"Infomatrix" (2018)</u>
- Euler Olympiad in Mathematics (2018)
- 5.5 band in *IELTS* (2018)
- Red Diploma of secondary education (2019)
- 3rd place in film festival "FilmFest 2022" (2022)

Zhassulan Serikuly

Front-end Developer

EXPERIENCE



🔯 ТОО "КасХИМ"

June, 2021 - August, 2021 / 3 months Role: IT Specialist

Atyrau, Kazakhstan

Tech stack: Python

Responsibilities: Perform assembly and installation of technical and software tools for the normal operation of the terminal. Install all the software you need to get started. Carrying out routine maintenance.

TechnoPark SDU

September, 2021 - February, 2022 / 5 months

Almaty, Kazakhstan

Role: Front-end Developer

Tech stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Responsibilities: Creating a web page based on design layouts, that is, layout using HTML and CSS. Binding to the user interface of scripts that provide visualization and animation of the site pages. Providing the required level of UI and UX.

Jops Optics

April, 2022 - May, 2022 / 1 month

Almaty, Kazakhstan

Role: SMM & Model

Responsibilities: Demonstration of glasses models during their manufacture. Posing for sketches, as well as for photo and video shooting.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Young's Store

Description: Website for a shop that sells stylish Korean clothes. Here you can watch

for the products, main information about co., make an order and also

apply for a job. Front-end. Adapted.

Tech stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript https://github.com/zhassik23/Store

Kazakhstan map and souvenir

Description: The project consists of a map of Kazakhstan, the main purpose of which is to describe Kazakhstan and its features by scanning a special gr-code

that will be with this souvenir. Inside of the scanned link will be provided a web service where full information about Kazakhstan, its distincts, culture, history, religion, interests of nature and some cities, etc.

Tech stack: Fusion 360°, Corel Draw

https://github.com/zhassik23/Kazakhstan-map-souvenir

Supermarket sales

Graduation year:

Faculty:

Speciality:

Description: Analyzing products in several markets and visualizing by different plots.

Tech stack: Python/Matplotlib/Pandas/Seaborn https://github.com/zhassik23/Supermarket-sales

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATES

Name of school/institution: National School-Gymnasium №13

Location: Atyrau, Kazakhstan Period: 2008 - 2014

Name of school/institution: Bilim-Innovation Lyceum (KTL)

Atyrau, Kazakhstan Location: 2014 - 2019 Period:

Name of school/institution: Suleyman Demirel University (SDU) Kaskelen, Almaty, Kazakhstan Location:

2019-2023

"Engineering and Natural Sciences"

Information Systems

HTML, CSS, and Javascript for Web Developers (Coursera) May 2021 Front-End Web Development with React (Coursera) April 2022